module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'In March 2019, what aircraft was grounded due to an erroneous software system?', 
    a: 'Airbus A340',
    b: 'Airbus A380-800',
    c: 'Boeing 737 MAX',
    d: 'Boeing 777',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'How many cards are in a standard deck including the joker cards?', 
    a: '54',
    b: '52',
    c: '50',
    d: '56',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is a baby goat called?', 
    a: 'Fawn',
    b: 'Veal',
    c: 'Calf',
    d: 'Kid',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'In the US Government, who is in charge of the Executive Branch?', 
    a: 'The President',
    b: 'The Chief Justice',
    c: 'Congress',
    d: 'Senate',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What was the first music video played on MTV?', 
    a: 'Da Ya Think I\'m Sexy',
    b: 'Money For Nothing',
    c: 'In the Air Tonight',
    d: 'Video Killed the Radio Star',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is NOT a Taco Bell Menu item?', 
    a: 'Nacho Fries',
    b: 'Chaluptra',
    c: 'Crunchwrap',
    d: 'Gordita',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Where is New Glasgow located?', 
    a: 'Nova Scotia',
    b: 'Brazil',
    c: 'Ireland',
    d: 'Holland',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is an ingredient in brown sugar?', 
    a: 'Corn Syrup',
    b: 'Agave Nectar',
    c: 'Maple Syrup',
    d: 'Molasses',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'What was the name of the Jetsons family dog?', 
    a: 'Neptune',
    b: 'Astro',
    c: 'Comet',
    d: 'Spike',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which genre of music typically features the double bass drum?', 
    a: 'House',
    b: 'Heavy Metal',
    c: 'EDM',
    d: 'Folk',
    answer: 'b'
  },
];